export const quizDB = [
	{
		id: "1",
		title: "anime manga",
		questions: [
			{
				question: `Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Phasellus nec leo nunc. Sed cursus
                 consequat ligulaasdas`,
				options: [
					"aslmkalskdmsa",
					"alskmaslkdmslkdm",
					"asjdnakjsjaskdja",
					"alkssmasdlksd",
				],
				answer: 0,
			},
			{
				question: `Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Phasellus nec leo nunc. Sed cursus
                 consequat ligula`,
				options: [
					"aslmkalskdmsa",
					"alskmaslkdmslkdm",
					"asjdnakjsjaskdja",
					"alkssmasdlksd",
				],
				answer: 1,
			},
			{
				question: `Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Phasellus nec leo nunc. Sed cursus
                 consequat ligula`,
				options: [
					"aslmkalskdmsa",
					"alskmaslkdmslkdm",
					"asjdnakjsjaskdja",
					"alkssmasdlksd",
				],
				answer: 3,
			},
		],
	},
	{
		id: "2",
		title: "movies",
		questions: [
			{
				question: `Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Phasellus nec leo nunc. Sed cursus
             consequat ligula`,
				options: [
					"aslmkalskdmsa",
					"alskmaslkdmslkdm",
					"asjdnakjsjaskdja",
					"alkssmasdlksd",
				],
				answer: 0,
			},
			{
				question: `Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Phasellus nec leo nunc. Sed cursus
             consequat ligula`,
				options: [
					"aslmkalskdmsa",
					"alskmaslkdmslkdm",
					"asjdnakjsjaskdja",
					"alkssmasdlksd",
				],
				answer: 1,
			},
			{
				question: `Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Phasellus nec leo nunc. Sed cursus
             consequat ligula`,
				options: [
					"aslmkalskdmsa",
					"alskmaslkdmslkdm",
					"asjdnakjsjaskdja",
					"alkssmasdlksd",
				],
				answer: 3,
			},
		],
	},
	{
		id: "3",
		title: "books",
		questions: [
			{
				question: `Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Phasellus nec leo nunc. Sed cursus
             consequat ligula`,
				options: [
					"aslmkalskdmsa",
					"alskmaslkdmslkdm",
					"asjdnakjsjaskdja",
					"alkssmasdlksd",
				],
				answer: 0,
			},
			{
				question: `Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Phasellus nec leo nunc. Sed cursus
             consequat ligula`,
				options: [
					"aslmkalskdmsa",
					"alskmaslkdmslkdm",
					"asjdnakjsjaskdja",
					"alkssmasdlksd",
				],
				answer: 1,
			},
			{
				question: `Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Phasellus nec leo nunc. Sed cursus
             consequat ligula`,
				options: [
					"aslmkalskdmsa",
					"alskmaslkdmslkdm",
					"asjdnakjsjaskdja",
					"alkssmasdlksd",
				],
				answer: 3,
			},
		],
	},
	{
		id: "4",
		title: "tv",
		questions: [
			{
				question: `Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Phasellus nec leo nunc. Sed cursus
             consequat ligula`,
				options: [
					"aslmkalskdmsa",
					"alskmaslkdmslkdm",
					"asjdnakjsjaskdja",
					"alkssmasdlksd",
				],
				answer: 0,
			},
			{
				question: `Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Phasellus nec leo nunc. Sed cursus
             consequat ligula`,
				options: [
					"aslmkalskdmsa",
					"alskmaslkdmslkdm",
					"asjdnakjsjaskdja",
					"alkssmasdlksd",
				],
				answer: 1,
			},
			{
				question: `Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Phasellus nec leo nunc. Sed cursus
             consequat ligula`,
				options: [
					"aslmkalskdmsa",
					"alskmaslkdmslkdm",
					"asjdnakjsjaskdja",
					"alkssmasdlksd",
				],
				answer: 3,
			},
		],
	},
];
